# Hui En Lin

E-mail: huienlin.game@gmail.com Website: https://hui-en.me

I am a communicative programmer with a great deal of experience in collaborating with people from different roles. As a programmer with professional experience in developing products with Unity for over four years, I can implement many kinds of gameplay features and optimize efficiently.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Unity Software Engineer**

Seekrtech, Taiwan (Sep 2017 – Jun 2021)

- Worked on a mobile to-do list app from scratch with gamification feature in a cross-functional team
- Implemented all game mechanics in C# with UniRx, designed code architecture and database schema
- Defined art assets standard, developing level design and UI building tools, improving productivity
- Executed project in Scrum framework, scheduling work accurately

## Front-End Engineer (Internship)

Seekrtech, Taiwan (Jul 2017 – Sep 2017; Jul 2018 – Sep 2018)

- Developed several websites for company and products with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and frameworks.
- Refactored browser extension, developed new features, and connected server APIs, increasing number of users by 60,000
- Defined static website skeleton for future product webpages, reducing time for developing a new website

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

#### **Game Programmer**

Hourglass: Project Norn (Oct 2017 – May 2018)

- Implemented several significant gameplay features such as player movement, item interaction, and boss AI
- Collaborated with game designer, designing system and keeping it implementable
- Imported shader effects for visual experience, making graphics more lively
- Presented game at largest student exhibition in Taiwan, with over 80,000 people visiting

## Game Programmer

Pinka (Jan 2016 – May 2017)

- Designed game mechanics with educational features to teach English vocabulary
- Implemented several significant gameplay features in C# with Unity, such as user input, UI, combat system, and map generation
- Won 1st place in educational digital media competition, which contained over 20 other projects from three different universities eligible for rewards

## **EDUCATION**

Utrecht University, Netherlands (Sep 2022 - Present)

Degree: Master in Game and Media Technology

Yuan Ze University, Taiwan (Sep 2015 – Jun 2018)

Degree: Bachelor of Science in Information Communication

### **TECHNICAL SCKILLS**

Programming skills: C++, C#, UE4 Blueprint, GLSL, Git, SQL, shell script

Software: Unity, Unreal Engine, Open GL

Collaboration / Knowledge: Scrum, Git Flow, Design Pattern, OOP, Desktop, Android / iOS